<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>Fede’s intern 🥊 / @fede_intern</title>
    <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern</link>
    <description>Twitter feed for: @fede_intern. Generated by nitter.freedit.eu
</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <ttl>40</ttl>
    <image>
      <title>Fede’s intern 🥊 / @fede_intern</title>
      <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern</link>
      <url>https://nitter.freedit.eu/pic/pbs.twimg.com%2Fprofile_images%2F1880254570242158592%2FythT4MNQ_400x400.jpg</url>
      <width>128</width>
      <height>128</height>
    </image>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @fede_intern: &quot;What is Aligned?&quot;

Our Co-Founder and Head of Engineering, @MauroAligned, breaks it down in detail for @dabit3 from @eigenlayer during their conversation on the Infinite Layers stream.

Watch below. 👇🏻</title>
        <dc:creator>@alignedlayer</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>"What is Aligned?"<br>
<br>
Our Co-Founder and Head of Engineering, <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/MauroAligned" title="Mauro Toscano 🟩">@MauroAligned</a>, breaks it down in detail for <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/dabit3" title="nader dabit (bronze age arc)">@dabit3</a> from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/eigenlayer" title="EigenLayer">@eigenlayer</a> during their conversation on the Infinite Layers stream.<br>
<br>
Watch below. 👇🏻</p>
<img src="https://nitter.freedit.eu/pic/amplify_video_thumb%2F1883159378590912512%2Fimg%2FZjzyBVBbbd6wxZZZ.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 14:26:18 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/alignedlayer/status/1883159464527941973#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/alignedlayer/status/1883159464527941973#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>True and sad. I was expecting the UK to do something interesting and it never happened.</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>True and sad. I was expecting the UK to do something interesting and it never happened.</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/Zac_Aztec/status/1883039537666114046#m">nitter.freedit.eu/Zac_Aztec/status/1883039537666114046#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 13:50:20 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1883150411932242432#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1883150411932242432#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Fully agree with everything.</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Fully agree with everything.</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/radi_cojbasic/status/1882880926608162850#m">nitter.freedit.eu/radi_cojbasic/status/1882880926608162850#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 00:31:39 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882949418753962208#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882949418753962208#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @fede_intern: Fantastic post which completely changed my thinking on native rollups.

There&apos;s an inherent tension in Ethereum between the following goals:

(1) Embrace diversity of people and opinions and enjoy the innovation that comes with it.

(2) Make Ethereum (and all of its L2s) feel like a single, unified ecosystem.

Ethereum is the only ecosystem today with dozens of independent (and independently funded!) core development teams building the protocol. This is a huge strength and the talent of the people contributing to Ethereum is unmatched anywhere.

But does this also create some tension? Absolutely.

While there&apos;s a lot that unites them, each L2 team has its own vision, its own goals, and its own tech stack. It would be a lot easier to build a single unified ecosystem with one spec (and even one developer team).

But if we did that, we&apos;d lose the diversity and innovation that makes Ethereum stand out. The EVM and Solidity emerged from Ethereum devs, but so did @CairoLang, so did @FhenixIO&apos;s FHE-powered EVM,  so did  @fuel_network&apos;s FuelVM, and so did Arbitrum Stylus which enables WASM/Rust/C/C++ programs on Ethereum. 

In Vitalik&apos;s words:
Instead, Vitalik advocates for taking the step to unify the Ethereum experience while maintaining its unique character and diversity. Some of this is in the form of concrete technical features like chain-specific addresses. But the bulk of this is deep coordination between teams,  finding common ground between them and working together to build interop tech that unites us.

Enter native rollups.

Before today, I was pretty bearish on the notion of native rollups to be honest, as the way I had heard them pitched was a push for all chains to become homogenous and unify around a specific implementation of the EVM.

I thought this was a bad idea because while it might make interop easier in the short term, it would stifle Ethereum&apos;s innovation in the long term. 

But Vitalik presented it a bit differently than I had understood:

The way I understand Vitalik&apos;s view of native rollups is kinda like &quot;refactoring&quot; code. There are a lot of rollups that utilize the EVM and we should coordinate around a standard for that. Rather than have each rollup build this out independently, we should factor out this common feature and even add more native support for these functionalities.

But importantly we should do it in a way that allows rollups to extend the VM, and build a culture that continues to value innovation. 

Native rollups doesn&apos;t mean that that everyone has to be homogenous; it just means that we should find the &quot;common core&quot; and build those components together so we can waste less time on reinventing the wheel. Some rollups may stop there and just use the shared code, while others will innovate on top of it, building custom execution environments.

There&apos;s still a lot of research that needs to go into &quot;can we do this&quot;. Can we actually build a &quot;common core&quot; rollup that enables innovation? What does this common core look like and how can we build it in a way that all existing EVM rollups can get behind it and benefit from it.

Yes, it&apos;s early days. Yes there&apos;s a ton of research to be done. But as a vision, I think this is fantastic and I&apos;m excited about the future of an Ethereum that&apos;s both interconnected and diverse.</title>
        <dc:creator>@sgoldfed</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Fantastic post which completely changed my thinking on native rollups.<br>
<br>
There's an inherent tension in Ethereum between the following goals:<br>
<br>
(1) Embrace diversity of people and opinions and enjoy the innovation that comes with it.<br>
<br>
(2) Make Ethereum (and all of its L2s) feel like a single, unified ecosystem.<br>
<br>
Ethereum is the only ecosystem today with dozens of independent (and independently funded!) core development teams building the protocol. This is a huge strength and the talent of the people contributing to Ethereum is unmatched anywhere.<br>
<br>
But does this also create some tension? Absolutely.<br>
<br>
While there's a lot that unites them, each L2 team has its own vision, its own goals, and its own tech stack. It would be a lot easier to build a single unified ecosystem with one spec (and even one developer team).<br>
<br>
But if we did that, we'd lose the diversity and innovation that makes Ethereum stand out. The EVM and Solidity emerged from Ethereum devs, but so did <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/CairoLang" title="CairoLang">@CairoLang</a>, so did <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/FhenixIO" title="Fhenix">@FhenixIO</a>'s FHE-powered EVM,  so did  <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/fuel_network" title="Fuel">@fuel_network</a>'s FuelVM, and so did Arbitrum Stylus which enables WASM/Rust/C/C++ programs on Ethereum. <br>
<br>
In Vitalik's words:<br>
Instead, Vitalik advocates for taking the step to unify the Ethereum experience while maintaining its unique character and diversity. Some of this is in the form of concrete technical features like chain-specific addresses. But the bulk of this is deep coordination between teams,  finding common ground between them and working together to build interop tech that unites us.<br>
<br>
Enter native rollups.<br>
<br>
Before today, I was pretty bearish on the notion of native rollups to be honest, as the way I had heard them pitched was a push for all chains to become homogenous and unify around a specific implementation of the EVM.<br>
<br>
I thought this was a bad idea because while it might make interop easier in the short term, it would stifle Ethereum's innovation in the long term. <br>
<br>
But Vitalik presented it a bit differently than I had understood:<br>
<br>
The way I understand Vitalik's view of native rollups is kinda like "refactoring" code. There are a lot of rollups that utilize the EVM and we should coordinate around a standard for that. Rather than have each rollup build this out independently, we should factor out this common feature and even add more native support for these functionalities.<br>
<br>
But importantly we should do it in a way that allows rollups to extend the VM, and build a culture that continues to value innovation. <br>
<br>
Native rollups doesn't mean that that everyone has to be homogenous; it just means that we should find the "common core" and build those components together so we can waste less time on reinventing the wheel. Some rollups may stop there and just use the shared code, while others will innovate on top of it, building custom execution environments.<br>
<br>
There's still a lot of research that needs to go into "can we do this". Can we actually build a "common core" rollup that enables innovation? What does this common core look like and how can we build it in a way that all existing EVM rollups can get behind it and benefit from it.<br>
<br>
Yes, it's early days. Yes there's a ton of research to be done. But as a vision, I think this is fantastic and I'm excited about the future of an Ethereum that's both interconnected and diverse.</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/VitalikButerin/status/1882649065139384600#m">nitter.freedit.eu/VitalikButerin/status/1882649065139384600#m</a></p>
<img src="https://nitter.freedit.eu/pic/media%2FGiDzVAQXgAAhtw8.png" style="max-width:250px;" />
<img src="https://nitter.freedit.eu/pic/media%2FGiD5TFQW4AAhOzu.png" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:40:28 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/sgoldfed/status/1882785543135568102#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/sgoldfed/status/1882785543135568102#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Thanks for the quote!</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Thanks for the quote!</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/ezklxyz/status/1882850950697845000#m">nitter.freedit.eu/ezklxyz/status/1882850950697845000#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 23:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882927503096119758#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882927503096119758#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Making great progress</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Making great progress</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1875607586009182335#m">nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1875607586009182335#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 20:17:57 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882885574077686110#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882885574077686110#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @fede_intern: epic sequencing call #17!

Many founders, including 10 rollup founders, shared their support for based and/or native rollups. Below are some their quotes. 1h45min YouTube recording coming ASAP :)

Part 1—based and native rollups

Ben Jones from @Optimism: &quot;Let&apos;s get this right. Optimism is willing to support based sequencing and native execution. It&apos;s wartime.&quot;

Nick Johnson from @ensdomains: &quot;You can count Namechain as based-pilled and native-pilled [...] and consider us fully onboard.&quot;

Jesse Pollak from @base: &quot;We need to scale and connect the Ethereum ecosystem and based sequencing and native execution feel like the tools to do it.&quot;

Tomasz Stanczak from @NethermindEth: &quot;Based and native rollups feel super aligned, they are what we&apos;re super excited about.&quot; &quot;We will be experimenting with Surge, based rollups, and FABRIC.&quot;

Hayden Adams from @unichain: [couldn&apos;t make it; see recording for my Unichain take]

Steven Goldfeder from @arbitrum: &quot;Diversity makes Ethereum unique [...] We need to find a common core - which is a native rollup, but not stifle innovation on top of it. [...] We&apos;re excited to contribute to this direction [...] All of us want Ethereum to win.&quot;

Fede Carrone from @class_lambda: &quot;Based? For me, it clicked within seconds&quot;

Ye Zhang from @Scroll_ZKP: &quot;Based sequencing is an important way to stay in the same economic zone with Ethereum. [...] Native rollups are a super interesting idea!&quot;

Part 2—FABRIC: Fabric to Accelerate Based Rollup Infrastructure and Connectivity

Drew Van der Werff from @Commit_Boost: &quot;FABRIC is a shelling point to coordinate and stitch together some of the fragmentation that has emerged&quot;

mteam from @Spire_Labs: &quot;Spire is devoting developer resources to native rollups.&quot; &quot;We believe that a unified set of standards based rollups will lead to greater efficiency in development timelines, bring down costs for users, and establish a compatibility zone which is why we’re excited to announce our support of Fabric&quot;

Daniel Wang from @taikoxyz: &quot;we&apos;ve been waiting for the FABRIC standards so we can work together and provide a full solution&quot; &quot;Taiko is willing to contribute to the Fabric project to make sure we can divide and conquer the problems&quot;

Amir Forouzani from @puffer_finance: &quot;Based rollups were a no-brainer for us, [...] so were native rollups.&quot; &quot;FABRIC just makes so much sense, [...] these standardization efforts are so important&quot;

Demi Brener from @OpenZeppelin: &quot;We see based rollups as a promising path towards scaling Ethereum and billions of user.&quot; &quot;We are supportive of the FABRIC efforts and are willing to contribute.&quot;

Sam Batternally from @rise_chain: &quot;I am here to voice my support for FABRIC&quot; &quot;the signaling from Ethereum that this is the direction scaling is going which will be huge to pull off and attract more builders&quot;

Vitalik Buterin: &quot;our community thrives on open source, open research [...] It&apos;s amazing to see all of this interest and willingness to work together on sequencing and interoperability</title>
        <dc:creator>@drakefjustin</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>epic sequencing call #17!<br>
<br>
Many founders, including 10 rollup founders, shared their support for based and/or native rollups. Below are some their quotes. 1h45min YouTube recording coming ASAP :)<br>
<br>
Part 1—based and native rollups<br>
<br>
Ben Jones from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/Optimism" title="Optimism.eth">@Optimism</a>: "Let's get this right. Optimism is willing to support based sequencing and native execution. It's wartime."<br>
<br>
Nick Johnson from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/ensdomains" title="ens.eth">@ensdomains</a>: "You can count Namechain as based-pilled and native-pilled [...] and consider us fully onboard."<br>
<br>
Jesse Pollak from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/base" title="Base">@base</a>: "We need to scale and connect the Ethereum ecosystem and based sequencing and native execution feel like the tools to do it."<br>
<br>
Tomasz Stanczak from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/NethermindEth" title="Nethermind">@NethermindEth</a>: "Based and native rollups feel super aligned, they are what we're super excited about." "We will be experimenting with Surge, based rollups, and FABRIC."<br>
<br>
Hayden Adams from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/unichain" title="Unichain">@unichain</a>: [couldn't make it; see recording for my Unichain take]<br>
<br>
Steven Goldfeder from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/arbitrum" title="Arbitrum (💙,🧡)">@arbitrum</a>: "Diversity makes Ethereum unique [...] We need to find a common core - which is a native rollup, but not stifle innovation on top of it. [...] We're excited to contribute to this direction [...] All of us want Ethereum to win."<br>
<br>
Fede Carrone from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/class_lambda" title="LambdaClass">@class_lambda</a>: "Based? For me, it clicked within seconds"<br>
<br>
Ye Zhang from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/Scroll_ZKP" title="Scroll">@Scroll_ZKP</a>: "Based sequencing is an important way to stay in the same economic zone with Ethereum. [...] Native rollups are a super interesting idea!"<br>
<br>
Part 2—FABRIC: Fabric to Accelerate Based Rollup Infrastructure and Connectivity<br>
<br>
Drew Van der Werff from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/Commit_Boost" title="Commit-Boost 📻 🕶️ 🦇🔊">@Commit_Boost</a>: "FABRIC is a shelling point to coordinate and stitch together some of the fragmentation that has emerged"<br>
<br>
mteam from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/Spire_Labs" title="Spire🗼">@Spire_Labs</a>: "Spire is devoting developer resources to native rollups." "We believe that a unified set of standards based rollups will lead to greater efficiency in development timelines, bring down costs for users, and establish a compatibility zone which is why we’re excited to announce our support of Fabric"<br>
<br>
Daniel Wang from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/taikoxyz" title="Taiko.eth 🥁">@taikoxyz</a>: "we've been waiting for the FABRIC standards so we can work together and provide a full solution" "Taiko is willing to contribute to the Fabric project to make sure we can divide and conquer the problems"<br>
<br>
Amir Forouzani from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/puffer_finance" title="Puffer Finance 🐡">@puffer_finance</a>: "Based rollups were a no-brainer for us, [...] so were native rollups." "FABRIC just makes so much sense, [...] these standardization efforts are so important"<br>
<br>
Demi Brener from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/OpenZeppelin" title="OpenZeppelin">@OpenZeppelin</a>: "We see based rollups as a promising path towards scaling Ethereum and billions of user." "We are supportive of the FABRIC efforts and are willing to contribute."<br>
<br>
Sam Batternally from <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/rise_chain" title="RISE Chain">@rise_chain</a>: "I am here to voice my support for FABRIC" "the signaling from Ethereum that this is the direction scaling is going which will be huge to pull off and attract more builders"<br>
<br>
Vitalik Buterin: "our community thrives on open source, open research [...] It's amazing to see all of this interest and willingness to work together on sequencing and interoperability</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 18:43:26 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/drakefjustin/status/1882861787491778998#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/drakefjustin/status/1882861787491778998#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @fede_intern: Viva Ethereum!
Viva la computadora mundial!</title>
        <dc:creator>@EtherArgentina</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Viva Ethereum!<br>
Viva la computadora mundial!</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882822262111510692#m">nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882822262111510692#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 17:37:45 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/EtherArgentina/status/1882845256544399402#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/EtherArgentina/status/1882845256544399402#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @fede_intern: these guys are the real deal, best believe.</title>
        <dc:creator>@TulpaLab_</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>these guys are the real deal, best believe.</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882811582821871970#m">nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882811582821871970#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:23:55 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/TulpaLab_/status/1882826674250944848#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/TulpaLab_/status/1882826674250944848#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @fede_intern: Ethereum forever in every language! 🚀 Long live the decentralized future, the world computer, and all of us building on it. Viva Ethereum! 🌍💻</title>
        <dc:creator>@DeboisMaurice</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Ethereum forever in every language! 🚀 Long live the decentralized future, the world computer, and all of us building on it. Viva Ethereum! 🌍💻</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:07:19 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/DeboisMaurice/status/1882822497663594857#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/DeboisMaurice/status/1882822497663594857#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>以太坊萬歲
以太幣萬歲
世界計算機萬歲

Long live Ethereum
Long live Ethereum
Long live the world computer

Viva Ethereum
Viva Ethereum
Viva la computadora mundial</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>以太坊萬歲<br>
以太幣萬歲<br>
世界計算機萬歲<br>
<br>
Long live Ethereum<br>
Long live Ethereum<br>
Long live the world computer<br>
<br>
Viva Ethereum<br>
Viva Ethereum<br>
Viva la computadora mundial</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/VitalikButerin/status/1882811848350892517#m">nitter.freedit.eu/VitalikButerin/status/1882811848350892517#m</a></p>
<img src="https://nitter.freedit.eu/pic/media%2FGiEg3lKWUAAqT8L.jpg" style="max-width:250px;" />]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 16:06:23 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882822262111510692#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882822262111510692#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>The good thing for us about the current situation is that we’re experts in chaos and crisis. We get hired very often by projects in web2 and web3 that are in a huge engineering and management crisis. They pay us to turn things around. To deliver, prioritize, hire people, fire people, recommend what to do. We’re a small SWAT engineering and product team. 

Ethereum has a small crisis right now. All our engineers and companies have been trained at dealing with crisis 24/7. Hopefully our Argentina skills are useful for Ethereum in the years to come.</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>The good thing for us about the current situation is that we’re experts in chaos and crisis. We get hired very often by projects in web2 and web3 that are in a huge engineering and management crisis. They pay us to turn things around. To deliver, prioritize, hire people, fire people, recommend what to do. We’re a small SWAT engineering and product team. <br>
<br>
Ethereum has a small crisis right now. All our engineers and companies have been trained at dealing with crisis 24/7. Hopefully our Argentina skills are useful for Ethereum in the years to come.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:23:56 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882811582821871970#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882811582821871970#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @fede_intern: Decentralization doesn&apos;t matter until it starts to matter one day</title>
        <dc:creator>@toghrulmaharram</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Decentralization doesn't matter until it starts to matter one day</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/ayyyeandy/status/1882705439571534004#m">nitter.freedit.eu/ayyyeandy/status/1882705439571534004#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:16:49 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/toghrulmaharram/status/1882794691470794957#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/toghrulmaharram/status/1882794691470794957#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>I disagree with @ayyyeandy.

Bitcoin is the biggest asset, it enabled for the first time transfer of money between humans without trust and without intermediaries.

Ethereum is the second asset by market cap. It’s biggest feature is that it enabled trustless computation.

This shows that users and people care about decentralization.

I do agree that new products and blockchains don’t need this level of decentralization since they can’t compete with Bitcoin and Ethereum. So obviously new products have to choose to focus on performance, cost and marketing. 

That said if it’s not for decentralization crypto doesn’t make any sense. We already have enough online casinos and web2 companies. I have nothing against centralized solutions. I built too many of them and still build multiple web2 products. That said our ethos and core reason to exist as an industry is decentralization.</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>I disagree with <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/ayyyeandy" title="Andy">@ayyyeandy</a>.<br>
<br>
Bitcoin is the biggest asset, it enabled for the first time transfer of money between humans without trust and without intermediaries.<br>
<br>
Ethereum is the second asset by market cap. It’s biggest feature is that it enabled trustless computation.<br>
<br>
This shows that users and people care about decentralization.<br>
<br>
I do agree that new products and blockchains don’t need this level of decentralization since they can’t compete with Bitcoin and Ethereum. So obviously new products have to choose to focus on performance, cost and marketing. <br>
<br>
That said if it’s not for decentralization crypto doesn’t make any sense. We already have enough online casinos and web2 companies. I have nothing against centralized solutions. I built too many of them and still build multiple web2 products. That said our ethos and core reason to exist as an industry is decentralization.</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/ayyyeandy/status/1882705439571534004#m">nitter.freedit.eu/ayyyeandy/status/1882705439571534004#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 15:21:24 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882810942075105766#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882810942075105766#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>RT by @fede_intern: @class_lambda keeps showing up, taking on PRs, adding features requested by validators, and just supporting this effort. No questions asked, just digging in and shipping. Thank you for all this effort on supporting open source public goods for Ethereum.</title>
        <dc:creator>@DrewVdW</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/class_lambda" title="LambdaClass">@class_lambda</a> keeps showing up, taking on PRs, adding features requested by validators, and just supporting this effort. No questions asked, just digging in and shipping. Thank you for all this effort on supporting open source public goods for Ethereum.</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882797639957090579#m">nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882797639957090579#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:36:36 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/DrewVdW/status/1882799668658377052#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/DrewVdW/status/1882799668658377052#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>R to @fede_intern: PR 231, Hot-Reloading for Configuration: https://github.com/Commit-Boost/commit-boost-client/pull/231

PR 244, Batch Size for Validator Registration: https://github.com/Commit-Boost/commit-boost-client/pull/244

PR 228, Improved Logging for Better Insights: https://github.com/Commit-Boost/commit-boost-client/pull/228

PR 223, Enhanced SSV Network Support: https://github.com/Commit-Boost/commit-boost-client/pull/223</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>PR 231, Hot-Reloading for Configuration: <a href="https://github.com/Commit-Boost/commit-boost-client/pull/231">github.com/Commit-Boost/comm…</a><br>
<br>
PR 244, Batch Size for Validator Registration: <a href="https://github.com/Commit-Boost/commit-boost-client/pull/244">github.com/Commit-Boost/comm…</a><br>
<br>
PR 228, Improved Logging for Better Insights: <a href="https://github.com/Commit-Boost/commit-boost-client/pull/228">github.com/Commit-Boost/comm…</a><br>
<br>
PR 223, Enhanced SSV Network Support: <a href="https://github.com/Commit-Boost/commit-boost-client/pull/223">github.com/Commit-Boost/comm…</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:28:33 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882797642612420953#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882797642612420953#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Commit-Boost @Commit_Boost updates by @class_lambda:
- Hot-Reloading for Configuration: We&apos;ve implemented Hot-Reloading, allowing operators to update their settings seamlessly without restarting the system. This enhancement provides greater flexibility and ensures a smoother transition for node operators adopting Commit-Boost. PR 231
- Batch Size for Validator Registration: To address relay limitations, operators can now configure batch sizes for validator registration. This ensures Commit-Boost sends validators in manageable batches, tailored to each relay’s capacity, preventing failures caused by large single requests. PR 244
- Improved Logging for Better Insights: Based on feedback from node operators, we’ve enhanced the logs to now display the number of successfully registered validators. This update provides clearer visibility into operations, making it easier to monitor and troubleshoot effectively. PR 228
- Enhanced SSV Network Support: We’ve improved support for the SSV network, enabling users to easily select relays based on their operator ID. This update simplifies configuration and enhances efficiency for SSV users, making their experience more streamlined and intuitive. PR 223</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Commit-Boost <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/Commit_Boost" title="Commit-Boost 📻 🕶️ 🦇🔊">@Commit_Boost</a> updates by <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/class_lambda" title="LambdaClass">@class_lambda</a>:<br>
- Hot-Reloading for Configuration: We've implemented Hot-Reloading, allowing operators to update their settings seamlessly without restarting the system. This enhancement provides greater flexibility and ensures a smoother transition for node operators adopting Commit-Boost. PR 231<br>
- Batch Size for Validator Registration: To address relay limitations, operators can now configure batch sizes for validator registration. This ensures Commit-Boost sends validators in manageable batches, tailored to each relay’s capacity, preventing failures caused by large single requests. PR 244<br>
- Improved Logging for Better Insights: Based on feedback from node operators, we’ve enhanced the logs to now display the number of successfully registered validators. This update provides clearer visibility into operations, making it easier to monitor and troubleshoot effectively. PR 228<br>
- Enhanced SSV Network Support: We’ve improved support for the SSV network, enabling users to easily select relays based on their operator ID. This update simplifies configuration and enhances efficiency for SSV users, making their experience more streamlined and intuitive. PR 223</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:28:32 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882797639957090579#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882797639957090579#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Great drawing</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Great drawing</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/nixorokish/status/1882786069684592790#m">nitter.freedit.eu/nixorokish/status/1882786069684592790#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 14:12:36 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882793629431071048#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882793629431071048#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Believing that L2s are parasitic is delulu. It’s literally what makes Ethereum big and unique. The ones that move to based native will have the decentralization and interop of Ethereum and they will pay fees accordingly.</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>Believing that L2s are parasitic is delulu. It’s literally what makes Ethereum big and unique. The ones that move to based native will have the decentralization and interop of Ethereum and they will pay fees accordingly.</p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:23:59 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882781392838533136#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882781392838533136#m</link>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>One of the best things that Solana has that I believe Ethereum should explore is the Local Fee Markets (LFM). While buying $TRUMP or $MELANIA didn’t work at one point at least to me, normal SOL transfers worked well.</title>
        <dc:creator>@fede_intern</dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[<p>One of the best things that Solana has that I believe Ethereum should explore is the Local Fee Markets (LFM). While buying <a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/search?q=%23TRUMP">$TRUMP</a> or $MELANIA didn’t work at one point at least to me, normal SOL transfers worked well.</p>
<p><a href="https://nitter.freedit.eu/TrustlessState/status/1882776579912384711#m">nitter.freedit.eu/TrustlessState/status/1882776579912384711#m</a></p>]]></description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 13:17:45 GMT</pubDate>
        <guid>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882779826639286690#m</guid>
        <link>https://nitter.freedit.eu/fede_intern/status/1882779826639286690#m</link>
      </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
